This fixture begins with a clear voice and enough silence for the detector to settle.
Each caption line uses ordinary words so subtitle synchronization can focus on timing.
The third sentence is intentionally longer and gives the alignment code a wider speech island.
After a pause the speaker continues with another compact sentence for the next cue.
A reliable fixture needs variation in length without becoming a long audiobook.
This cue mentions video containers audio codecs and subtitle rewrites in plain language.
The next phrase arrives after silence so the voice activity detector can split the span.
Short captions still matter because real subtitle files often mix brief and longer lines.
Another sentence adds more timing evidence before the final codec cases begin.
Near the end we keep the same calm delivery and leave room for timing drift checks.
One more cue gives the stretch test a broader timeline across the fixture.
The final spoken cue closes the fixture with a simple sentence and a clean ending.